Finding Aid for the Edith Lillian Jones Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Edith Lillian Jones Collection
1898-1903
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0580
0.1 linear feet
Biography/History
Edith Lillian Jones, from Ruth Arkansas, received an L.I. degree from George Peabody College in 1903. She died later that year.
In 1980, the collection was donated by Sarah Isabelle Eckert, her niece.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains nine photographs and seven postcards.
- Photographs – (9)
  - Class Photo
  - Harrison, Eloise Ambler
  - Kate
  - Rowenian Literary Society, [1898]
    Dr. Clark, Edith Lillian Jones, remainder unidentified
  - Unidentified – Men – (3)
  - Unidentified – Woman
  - Wells, Beulah Stanlet
- Postcards – Peabody College – (7)
  - College Hall, [1903]
  - Corner of campus, [1903]
  - Ewing gymnasium, [1903]
  - Lindsley Hall, [1903]
  - Offices, [1903]
  - President’s Residence, [1903]
  - Winthrop Model School, [1903]